gogortons.com 2018-03-22

# Privacy Policy - Gorton’s Seafood

The web site you have entered is operated by Gorton’s, Inc. Gorton’s is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of information that is collected by Gorton’s on this web site and information collected by Gorton’s offline, such as when you enter a Gorton’s sweepstakes, contest or promotion, and how we use and protect that information. This Policy also tells you what to do if you do not want your Personal Information collected when you visit our web site, and how you can change information you have already provided to us. This Policy applies only to the Gorton’s web site and to information Gorton’s collects offline. For example, it does not apply to banners, sweepstakes and other advertisements or promotions we may sponsor or participate in on web sites owned by third parties.

Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By using our web site or entering into a Gorton’s sweepstakes, contest or promotion, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not provide any Personal Information (defined below) on this site or in any Gorton’s sweepstakes, contest or promotion.

If you choose not to provide Personal Information on this site or offline, you may not be able to do certain things, like access particular areas of the site, enter a sweepstakes or contest, or send us e-mail.

Collection of Personal Information

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information such as your name, street address, telephone number, screen name and email address. The site you entered may collect some or all of these types of Personal Information. Please be assured that Gorton’s will not collect any Personal Information from your visits to our sites, or otherwise, unless you provide this information voluntarily.

When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of the Personal Information as described in this Policy (see “Who to Contact” below). The site you entered may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party. Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose and we will not contact the third party again by e-mail unless and until the third party contacts us.

How We Use Your Information

When you supply Personal Information at this web site or offline, it will be used for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to enter you in a sweepstakes). It may also be used, with your consent, to contact you regarding other products, or Gorton’s related information, which may be of interest to you. At any time, however, you may opt out of such future contact. (See “Who to Contact” below.)

In the course of doing business, we employ other companies and individuals to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, we hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to fulfill orders you place, and to provide customer service. These agents may have access to personal information if it is needed to perform their functions for Gorton’s; however, they are prohibited from using it for other purposes and they are required to maintain the information in confidence.

We will not sell, trade, rent or give individually identifying information to third parties. At times we may provide Personal Information and aggregate statistics about our visitors, database entries, web traffic patterns, and related site information we collect on our web site to selected vendors or third parties to analyze solely to help us improve our products and our web sites. Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order.

Other Information We May Collect On Our Site

You may have heard of “cookies,” which are files or pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Gorton’s may use cookies to collect other information during your visit to our web site, such as the particular site areas you visit and the products or services you buy through our web site. We collect this information to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities at our sites. For example, a site can recognize that you have provided Personal Information to us and refrain from requesting the same information a second time.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Refusal of cookies at the site you entered may result in an inability to visit certain areas of the site or to receive personalized information when you visit the site.

In addition, we are constantly trying to improve how we promote our web sites. To help us do this, we may measure the effectiveness of our web presence by determining what you clicked on to get to our site.

Site measurement statistics may be used to personalize your web site experience, as well as to evaluate – anonymously and in the aggregate – statistics about usage of the web site. Information about your computer, such as your IP address (a number assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Internet), the type of Internet browser you are using and the type of computer operating system you are using may also be collected and linked to your Personal Information. This is to ensure that our web sites present the best web experience for visitors, and that they are an effective information resource.

Some of the pages you visit may also collect information through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs) that may be shared with third parties which directly support Gorton’s promotional activities and web site development. The information collected through the use of these pixel tags is not, however, personally identifiable, although it could be linked to your Personal Information.

Finally, we may supplement the information that you provide us with other information that we receive from third parties. We do this for marketing purposes in order to provide more targeted products and services to meet your needs.

Children

At the Gorton’s website, users are told that they must be 13 years or older before sending Personal Information. Users under age 13 should not submit any Personal Information to us.

Security of Information

We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure. All personally identifiable information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse.

Changes in Our Policy

Gorton’s reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. We will post any new policy here and we encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

Who to Contact

Please write to us at [info@gortons.com](mailto:info@gortons.com) or call us at 1-800-222-6846 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or to report any violations of the Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within 24 to 48 hours in most cases.

If you don’t want to be contacted in the future or would like us to correct or update your Personal Information in our records, please email us with your request at [info@gortons.com](mailto:info@gortons.com).
